-[insects chirping]
-[rumbling]
[dinosaurs bellowing]
[thudding]
[roars, screeches]
-[Darius] We thought it'd be fun.
-[fire crackling]
We thought we'd be safe, but...
we didn't realize the... horror
waiting for us on the island.
Claws...
Teeth...
-Screaming...
-[gasps]
-[Darius] So much screaming.
-How much screaming?
Shh! He's getting to the good part.
The T. rex stalked closer.
Her jaws opened wide.
[camera shutter clicks]
What? Huh?
For the vlog.
Keep telling your little story.
[sighs]
Oh, here we go.
-The T. rex sta--
-[Brooklynn] Dang!
-Ugh!
-Out of space. Wait, I'm sorry, hold on.
I just don't wanna delete
my selfie on Everest, you know?
Ooh!
-Maybe I should start over.
-[Ben] No!
In fact, you can just stop.
Dude, chill. He's not even telling
the story right now.
And how is your grip this strong?
So, the T. rex stalked--
Shouldn't we call Yasmina over?
I bet she'd love this story.
Maybe she wants to be by herself.
I don't understand.
You know how sometimes
people just wanna be left alone?
[chuckles] Kenji, you're hilarious.
I think she's just shy and doesn't know
how to make camp friends.
-[thunder crashes]
-[gasps, whimpers]
-[all gasping, screaming]
-Maybe we should go inside.
[Ben] Way ahead of you!
-Hurry!
-[Kenji] Aw, man!
[Sammy] Oh, it's coming down fast.
[Brooklynn] Well,
that was a waste of time.
[scoffs]
Thanks, Brooklynn.
[thunder crashes]
Darius, it wasn't that great of a story.
I wasn't engrossed or anything.
[Brooklynn] Just don't touch my phone.
How does that sound?
[Kenji] Let's decide this
with a game of foose.
Oh, my pages got wet.
-You need a friend!
-[yelps] What?
I'm such a ding-dong!
You're alone. And when I feel alone,
having a friend around sure is nice.
I could use a friend,
and you probably could, too.
So I thought, "Yasmina needs someone
to make the first friendship move,"
so, here I am!
Um, I lost you around "ding-dong."
[gasps] Is that a scrapbook?
I love scrapbooking.
We can make one together.
Pull you out of your shell.
I'm pretty happy in my shell.
No one likes the shell.
It stops people from getting to know you.
Bingo!
-I know you're just shy!
-Can't hear you in my shell!
[low growl]
-[Darius] Yes!
-[Sammy] This is gonna be so much fun!
[Ben] Oh, man! I'm driving.
We get to drive gyrospheres? Cool!
Saddle up, dudes and dudettes.
We're going on a cattle drive,
but with dinosaurs!
It's a dino drive!
And just to be clear,
all these dinosaurs are herbivores, right?
Well, they only chewed
on the last kid a little,
so we're, like, 99 percent sure
they're cool.
[whimpers]
Park personnel are moving
a group of dinosaurs
to fresh grazing lands across the island,
and we get to ride along behind the herd.
Are you kidding me?
Dinosaur migration patterns are my jam!
You may wanna consider a new jam, bro.
So, uh, you sure these things
are waterproof?
Looking pretty grim out here
and hair this awesome does not come easy.
Your hair is gonna be fine, Kenji.
Storm has already moved
up the coast away from us.
Cool! Time to show these fools
what a gyrosphere master can do.
[Roxie] No way!
You are riding with Ben,
as a passenger.
But-- Seriously? But he's so, uh...
Whoa! [grunts]
-Live it up, tough guy.
-[groans]
This is gonna be so sick.
Right?
Now we're in a shell together.
A shell for two.
Yay.
Everyone, seat belts at all times.
Well, what you waiting for, bud?
Right. Um, is there a gyrosphere
I could drive solo or--
Darius, you need to ride
with your fellow campers.
Bond, live the camp life,
share your story, man.
Yeah, I tried last night, but, um...
not everyone was on board.
Buddy, you can't give up.
You need to get out there and you show
those other kids what you got.
Be yourself, Darius.
Teenagers can be very accepting
if you just give them half a chance.
Do they not have teenagers in England?
[inhales, exhales]
Hey, Brooklynn. Are you as stoked as I am
for our gyrosphere adventure?
Sure, whatevs.
[door hisses]
All righty, campers.
The headsets are for emergencies.
You can always reach us on channel six.
Let the herding begin!
-[Sammy] Whoo! See ya!
-[Kenji] Yes!
[crashes]
Okay, now.
Uh, slow and steady wins the race.
Huh! I'm really getting the hang of this!
[bellows]
Are you seeing this?
Whoa!
What's your favorite color? Favorite food?
Favorite color of food?
-Orange, orange, and orange.
-[laughs]
Jokes. I love jokes.
Ooh, what do you
and your friends do for fun?
I train... alone...
quietly.
Really? Dang!
I'm used to people all around 24-7.
My sisters, Daddy, Mama,
Abuela, the cattle. [chuckles]
My mom says I have a knack for dealing
with critters, and that in-- Whoa!
[exhales]
How awesome is this?
We're, like, so close!
Brooklynn?
[Brooklynn] "Used to be cool"?
"You made Jurassic World boring"?
"Lame." "Lame."
"No one likes you anymore."
Uh, hey, can you believe
that an ankylosaurus' tail
is strong enough to shatter bone?
Can you believe I don't care?
[sighs] I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I-- I'm just... having one of those days.
There's a lot of pressure when
your whole life is about being popular,
and I'm not like you.
I can't just tell a lame story
and move on.
It wasn't that lame.
Trust me, it was.
It totally was, but you're not even fazed.
I just need people to... to like m--
You wouldn't understand.
[Kenji] Of course I don't understand,
'cause you are literally
the worst driver I've ever seen, bruh.
If by "worst" you mean "safest,"
then, yes, yes, I am.
So not a compliment.
Now, come on. Faster, faster, faster!
[groans]
[thunder rumbles]
I thought you said
the storm rolled up the coast.
Oh, it must have rolled back down.
It's okay.
Other than mussing up Kenji's hair,
what's the worst that could happen?
[thunder crashes]
[bellows]
-[growls]
-[bellows]
Hey, gang, new plan.
Storm's getting worse,
so we're all going back to camp.
Fun, right?
-Aw, man!
-Are you serious?
Don't blame me. Blame the storm.
I blame them both.
[Darius] We're not gonna let a little rain
stop us, are we?
When else will we get the chance
to ride alongside a herd of dinosaurs?
Sorry, can't risk it.
But, Dave, I'm sure under you and Roxie's
capable leadership, we'll--
-This is not up for discussion.
-[static crackles]
Hello, hello! Roxie here.
Can you hear me? Anyone?
-[static crackles]
-[indistinct chatter]
Okay, new, new plan.
Storm's interfering with the radio,
so Rox and I will drive ahead
and tell the others we're pulling out.
We'll be right back.
Stay together and stay behind the herd.
[thunder crashes]
[bellows]
That sinoceratops is gonna get lost.
We need to go after her.
You heard Dave.
Let's just chill out and wait here.
I've read everything
about sinoceratops' behavior.
We can get her.
Plus, your followers might really love
a thrilling dino-chase.
[Darius chuckles]
Wait. Are you guys going after her?
I really don't think that's a good idea.
-I've seen cattle spook before, and--
-Uh-huh. Let's go.
[Sammy] Wait, why are we following them?
-Oh, no! There's no way I'm--
-Great! I'll drive.
[roars]
Almost got you, girl.
[both gasp]
[Darius grunts]
Whoa, whoa! Whew!
Sorry. That was close.
Voilà! Instant phone mount.
Great idea. And also, ew.
-Well, just keep driving, dino-nerd.
-Sure thing, superstar.
[Brooklynn giggles]
[sinoceratops bellows]
Um, let's just everybody settle down
a bit.
-We don't wanna get too close or--
-[both scream]
Watch it, Ben. You almost hit us!
It wasn't me!
-You're gonna get us both killed!
-With you driving, we'll die of boredom.
-Give me! [grunts]
-Just-- Give me... [grunts]
-Bro!
-Come on, Darius, get closer!
Someone flank her on the other side
and we can lead her back to the herd.
Wait, you'll scare her. Ah!
Let the big dogs handle this, cowgirl.
Sino sandwich, baby! Hoo!
[growls]
[giggling]
I'll cut her off. It'll be fine, Sammy.
No, he's gonna make her bolt.
This isn't the way to do this.
We gotta calm her down.
[bellows]
Listen up, y'all. We gotta get her
before she goes and spooks the whole herd.
-Stay to the outside or--
-[Kenji] We've got this.
Relax. Darius knows dinosaurs.
[growls]
[both screaming, grunting]
-[bellows]
-[Brooklynn screams]
-[Darius whimpers]
-[both screaming]
They're disappointed,
but they'll get over it.
-Better safe then...
-[bellows]
We've got multiple assets
straying from the herd. [gasps]
[both] The kids!
-[Roxie] Move!
-[crashes, creaks]
Duck!
[Brooklynn and Darius screaming]
[both panting, screaming]
[Brooklynn screams]
-Watch out!
-This thing's not going fast enough.
-Stego, 12 o'clock! Tail, tail, tail!
-Hang on!
Ah! I wanna go home!
[both scream]
[bellows]
Go, go, go, go, go!
-Low branch coming right at us!
-I see it. Let me concentrate.
[thunder crashes]
[both scream]
-[Sammy whimpers]
-[both panting]
Are we... alive? [sighs]
[Kenji screams, grunts]
Left! Back to right!
[grunts] Right! Back to left!
Fine, you drive! Just get us out of here!
-Finally! Let me show you how it's--
-[crashes]
[both grunting, screaming]
[both panting]
I think we lost them.
I think we lost everyone.
[gasps] Look!
Okay, think.
Sinoceratops are fast on open ground,
so we just need to corner her,
then we can get her back to the herd.
Great. Here we go!
Another Brooklynn exclusive!
Keep watching,
'cause it's about to get real!
Wait, wait! Brooklynn, wait!
-[sinoceratops bellows]
-[both scream]
[Brooklynn] Too real! Too real! [screams]
Come on! [gasps]
-[bellows]
-[both scream]
[whimpering]
-No! No!
-Whoa!
-[Darius] No! [whimpers]
-No! [screams]
-[both screaming]
-[bellows]
[pants]
[sighs]
[both panting]
[both chuckling]
-Huh?
-[gasps]
[mud squelching]
[thunder rumbling]
Good news-- this gives us a lot more time
to get to know each other.
We should do that... later.
Much, much later.
-First, we need to--
-[Brooklynn] Help! Can you hear us?
We're stuck... mudhole and we're sinking!
Help!
Brooklynn? Brooklynn, can you hear me?
Where are you?
We gotta find them.
-Brooklynn? Darius?
-Guys!
Can you hear us?
Keep clearing away the b-- No, wait.
Pile it up. Pile it up. All of it.
-Just keep piling. Come on.
-Okay.
[Yasmina] Get that one.
[both grunt]
[Sammy whimpers]
-[grunting]
-[Sammy] We're coming, Brooklynn!
Hello? Hello? Can anybody hear me?
[huffs] Still no sign of-- Ben and Kenji?
[all screaming]
-[grunts]
-No.
[sniffs]
I'm pretty sure we're exceeding
the maximum occupancy in here.
I lost them. It's just static.
[thunder crashes]
-[Darius] Help!
-[Brooklynn] Somebody, please!
I hear them! They're over there!
[Darius] We're in a sinkhole!
[both grunting]
It won't budge.
The mud is jamming the door shut.
-Try driving out again.
-We'll only sink deeper.
Then you think of something,
Mr. Let's-Go-Corner-the-Dinosaur!
[both grunt]
-[Brooklynn] Anybody, help!
-[Darius] Help!
[grunting]
No!
[Darius sighs]
[both panting]
-[Sammy] Brooklynn? Darius?
-[gasps]
Hello? Sammy?
[Sammy] Do you read me?
We're coming to help!
[gasps]
-[both] Help!
-[Brooklynn] Get us out of here!
Roxie! Dave!
We've got a real emergency here!
[grunts] I can't grab ahold of it.
-[both grunting]
-It's too heavy.
[Ben exclaims] It's gonna pull you under!
[both grunt]
[Ben] Uh, guys?
-[growling]
-[whimpers, grunts]
-[bellows]
-[pants]
What if...
I've got an idea.
What are you doing?
What? Wait!
[bellows]
-[roars]
-Ah!
-Hey.
-[groans]
I get it.
It's hard to trust strangers.
It's a scary world out there.
But...
I'll trust you if you trust me.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
-Whoa.
-[Darius] Guys?
[Brooklynn] Real touching and all,
but we're still gonna die!
-[Darius] Help!
-Hurry!
[grunts]
[Brooklynn] Got it!
[muffled scream]
-Hurry, Sammy!
-[grunts] On it!
Come on, girl. Easy.
[low growl]
[Sammy] That's it.
Nice and slow.
Let's go. You've got this.
[grunts]
Hey.
[laughs]
-[all cheering]
-It worked!
Whoo-hoo! [chuckles] All right! All right!
Cowgirl for the win!
-Woot! Woot!
-[vehicle approaching]
[Sammy] Hey, look! It's Dave and Roxie!
-Hey!
-[Ben sighs]
[sinoceratops bellows]
You could have been killed!
What were you thinking?
That we found a lost dinosaur...
and Darius and Brooklynn.
Don't ask me how I did it, but I did it.
-[Brooklynn laughing]
-[Roxie] What?
[Brooklynn] That's the funniest thing
I've heard all day!
-[Yasmina] Your eyes were closed.
-Now stay in your bunks, you hear me?
-[Sammy] Weren't you crying at one point?
-[Kenji] Hey, I helped!
-[Brooklynn] Oh, my gosh, he's serious.
-[Yasmina] Wow, Kenji.
[clears throat]
Uh... [clears throat]
I...
If everyone would have listened to you...
If I had listened,
we wouldn't have had any problems.
I'm not so great at trusting new people.
So, my favorite color is black,
my favorite food is pizza, and...
this is what I was doing before.
I started drawing to kill time
during track meets.
I'm not very good, so you probably...
probably won't even like them.
I don't like them.
I love them!
I knew we were gonna be friends!
Not really a-- a hugger.
You are now!
[Brooklynn] I managed to get
all the mud off,
which is more than I can say
for these fingernails.
Never a dull day
at Camp Cretaceous, right?
Hey, what's up?
I thought I knew everything
about dinosaurs, but...
all I did was mess up today. [sighs]
I... I just wanted...
People to like you?
Yeah.
Guess we have that in common.
Well, tomorrow's a new day.
And, thanks to you, I've got a new video
to show the Brooklanders,
so, um, I'm gonna go edit it and post.
[chuckles]
Later, dino-nerd.
Oh, and then the sino went boom!
And then Brooklynn was like... [screams]
And then Kenji saved the day... again.
Yeah, that's not at all what happened.
-Just making your story better, bruh.
-[chuckles]
[Brooklynn in video] Look that way.
Wait, come over here.
[distorted audio]
[normal audio] Look that way.
Wait, come over here.
Do you guys even know
how to do interviews?
Darius, stand-- No!
Stand to your left.
No, your other left!
What the...?
[theme music playing]